{
  "id": 701,
  "themeId": 7,
  "name": "Writing and Reading accents Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “summer”?",
      "options": [
        "Été",
        "Étè",
        "Étë",
        "Étet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Été",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"it was\"?",
      "options": [
        "C’ètait",
        "C’étaît",
        "C’était",
        "C’étaît"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "C’était",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “forest”?",
      "options": [
        "Forêt",
        "Forèt",
        "Forest",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Forêt",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “father and mother”?",
      "options": [
        "Pére et mère",
        "Père et mére",
        "Père et mère",
        "Pére et mére"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Père et mère",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “window”?",
      "options": [
        "Fenétre",
        "Fenestre",
        "Fenëtre",
        "Fenêtre"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Fenêtre",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “where”?",
      "options": [
        "Oü",
        "Où",
        "Ou",
        "Oùé"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Où",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"party\"?",
      "options": [
        "Fète",
        "Feste",
        "Fête",
        "Féte"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Fête",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"disorderly place\"?",
      "options": [
        "Capharnaum",
        "Capharnaûm",
        "Capharnaùm",
        "Capharnaüm"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Capharnaüm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"task\"?",
      "options": [
        "Tâche",
        "Tache",
        "Tasche",
        "Täche"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tâche",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Christmas\" ?",
      "options": [
        "Noel",
        "Noël",
        "Noèl",
        "Noél"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Noël",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}